http://www.markle.org/online-privacy-policy

You are using an outdated browser. Some of the rich features of this site is not going to function on this browser. Consider updading your browser or using a newer browser.
About
Page Sections
About MarkleA Message from Zoë BairdOur PrinciplesOur ImpactBoard of DirectorsSenior TeamOur History
Quick Links
Careers
Conference Space
Events
Markle in the News
Media Releases
Past Initiatives
President's Letters
Zoë Baird Bio
Skillful
Page Sections
SkillfulSkillful StoriesOur PartnersMarkle Workforce Initiatives Advisory BoardSkillful In the News
Quick Links
Advisory Board
The State of American Jobs
Latest News
Rework America
Page Sections
Rework America™Rework America In The News
Quick Links
Health
About HealthOur ImpactSteering GroupConsumer Work GroupHIE Committee
National Security
About National SecurityPost-9/11 LegacyOur ImpactTask Force
Library
Quick Links
Our Book: America's Moment
Archive
Media Releases
Member Commentary
President's Letters
Financials
Videos
Policy
About
Page Sections
About MarkleA Message from Zoë BairdOur PrinciplesOur ImpactBoard of DirectorsSenior TeamOur History
Quick Links
Careers
Conference Space
Events
Markle in the News
Media Releases
Past Initiatives
President's Letters
Zoë Baird Bio
Skillful
Page Sections
SkillfulSkillful StoriesOur PartnersMarkle Workforce Initiatives Advisory BoardSkillful In the News
Quick Links
Advisory Board
The State of American Jobs
Latest News
Rework America
Page Sections
Rework America™Rework America In The News
Quick Links
Health
About HealthOur ImpactSteering GroupConsumer Work GroupHIE Committee
National Security
About National SecurityPost-9/11 LegacyOur ImpactTask Force
Library
Quick Links
Our Book: America's Moment
Archive
Media Releases
Member Commentary
President's Letters
Financials
Videos
Policy
About
Page Sections
About MarkleA Message from Zoë BairdOur PrinciplesOur ImpactBoard of DirectorsSenior TeamOur History
Quick Links
Careers
Conference Space
Events
Markle in the News
Media Releases
Past Initiatives
President's Letters
Zoë Baird Bio
Skillful
Page Sections
SkillfulSkillful StoriesOur PartnersMarkle Workforce Initiatives Advisory BoardSkillful In the News
Quick Links
Advisory Board
The State of American Jobs
Latest News
Rework America
Page Sections
Rework America™Rework America In The News
Quick Links
Health
About HealthOur ImpactSteering GroupConsumer Work GroupHIE Committee
National Security
About National SecurityPost-9/11 LegacyOur ImpactTask Force
Library
Quick Links
Our Book: America's Moment
Archive
Media Releases
Member Commentary
President's Letters
Financials
Videos
Policy
Online Privacy Policy
This Online Privacy Policy describes how Markle treats personal information and other data received from visitors to this Web site.
Information Collection
As a visitor to this Web site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with certain activities, however, the Markle Foundation may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an on-line form. Whether you elect to engage in those activities is entirely your option.
The Markle Foundation collects personal information when you register for a service offered by the Markle Foundation, respond to a user survey or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. "Personal information" is information that identifies, or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person to whom such information pertains (e.g., your name, address, e-mail address or phone number).
The Markle Foundation's server automatically records information that your browser sends when you visit this Web site. The server log may include such information as your URL, Internet Protocol address, browser type and language, the page that you request, and the date and time of your visit.
If you post a comment to a blog, videoconference or other similar service, we may collect the following personal information: your name, your e-mail address, your affiliation, and the comments that you post.
Uses of Collected Information
The Markle Foundation may use personal information in order to provide the services that you’ve requested.
The Markle Foundation may use personal information and other data for audit, research and analysis intended to improve and operate this Web site and services provided hereon.
If we intend to use personal information for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was initially provided, we will ask for your consent prior to that use. If you post a comment to a blog, videoconference or other similar service, your name, your affiliation, and the comment that you post will be considered public information. Your e-mail address will not be published or supplied to any 3rd party (except in the circumstances described below). We retain the right to use your e-mail address to send you information and updates. You may opt-out of these communications by following the directions in each such communication.
Information Sharing
The Markle Foundation only shares personal information with other companies or individuals in the following limited circumstances:
We have your affirmative, "opt-in" consent for sharing of your personal information.
We engage third-parties to assist with the processing of personal information on our behalf. These third-party vendors and service providers include Rackspace (Web site hosting), SalesForce (customer relationship management (CRM)), Vimeo (video hosting), Mollom (spam filter), Vertical Response (e-mail distribution), Spark Street Digital (webcast), Sputnik Moment (CRM consultant), and Group SJR (web site maintenance).
We have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request; (b) enforce this Online Privacy Policy, or investigation of any suspected violations thereof; (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) or protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of the Markle Foundation, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
The Markle Foundation may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties. Such information does not identify you individually.
Information Security
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include:
periodic internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures; and
physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.
We may also use passwords to help verify your identity before granting access to certain services and functionalities. Should you elect to participate in such a password-protected service, we urge you to take appropriate precautions to protect your privacy (e.g., do not disclose your password to others; periodically change your password).
We restrict access to personal information to Markle Foundation employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve services in connection with which your personal information has been collected. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
Data Integrity
The Markle Foundation processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We periodically review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete and current, but we depend upon our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.
Links to Other Sites
This Web site contains links to other Web sites which may collect personal information. Unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that Web site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.
Accessing and Upgrading Personal Information
Upon your request, we will make good faith efforts to correct, update or delete your personal information. If you wish to correct, update or delete your personal information, please contact [email protected], or:
Markle Foundation
Attn: Communications
10 Rockefeller Plaza, 16th Floor
New York, NY 10020
Privacy Policy Information and Complaints
For more information about our privacy practices, or if you believe that there has been a violation of this Privacy Policy, please contact [email protected], or:
Markle Foundation
Attn: Managing Director & CFO
10 Rockefeller Plaza, 16th Floor
New York, NY 10020
If you are writing with respect to possible policy violations, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways which you believe the policy has been violated. We will then promptly investigate your complaint.
Changes in Privacy Policy
The Markle Foundation reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time in its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of this Web site. If, as the result of such changes, you wish to alter the ways in which we use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure as described under Accessing and Updating Personal Information.
Our Mission
Markle works to realize the potential of information technology to address previously intractable public problems for the economic security, health, and national security of all Americans.
About MarkleSkillfulRework AmericaAdvisory BoardHealthNational SecurityLibrary
Online Privacy PolicyFAQsTerms & ConditionsContact Us
Our Mission
Markle works to realize the potential of information technology to address previously intractable public problems for the economic security, health, and national security of all Americans.
About MarkleSkillfulRework AmericaAdvisory BoardHealthNational SecurityLibrary
Online Privacy PolicyFAQsTerms & ConditionsContact Us
About
Page Sections
About MarkleA Message from Zoë BairdOur PrinciplesOur ImpactBoard of DirectorsSenior TeamOur History Quick Links
CareersConference SpaceEventsMarkle in the NewsMedia ReleasesPast InitiativesPresident's LettersZoë Baird Bio
Skillful
Page Sections
SkillfulSkillful StoriesOur PartnersMarkle Workforce Initiatives Advisory BoardSkillful In the News Quick Links
About National SecurityPost-9/11 LegacyOur ImpactTask Force National Security
About HealthOur ImpactSteering GroupConsumer Work GroupHIE Committee
Library
Quick Links
Latest News
